那么现在要从菜单项里打开一个SettingsActivity(设置界面)
Now it's time to launch a settings activity from the menu item.
我们需要从两个地方打开这个activity  MainActivity和
We need to launch it from two places, the Main Activity and
DetailActivity
the Detail Activity.
然后  编译运行程序来检验功能是否有效
Afterwards, compile and run the app to make sure that it works.
这里就是MainActivity里的实现体
This is what it should look like from the.
当你点击Settings菜单的时候
Main Activity, if you tap on Settings menu,
程序会转向SettingsActivity
it should be bring you to the Settings Activity.
现在它应该是空白的  因为我们还没充实它的内容
It is expected for it to be blank, because we haven't populated it yet.
首先从DetailActivity开始
Now let's try the Detail Activity.
当你点击某个预报的时候  你会进入DetailActivity
If you tap on a Forecast, you can go into the Detail Activity and
然后你就可以进入SettingsActivity
then you can go into the Settings Activity.
完成任务并且验证你的程序运行出来是酱紫的
Complete the task and then verify that your app behavior is like this.
按照我之前提供的思路
In the directions that I just provided and
和这套课程的相关视频中  你会发现SettingsActivity
in the following videos of this course, you'll notice that the settings
在屏幕顶部有一个ActionBar
activity had an action bar at the top of the screen.
当程序中使用最新版本的SupportLibrary（该库包含在Android SDK中，用于支持更早版本的OS）
When building your app with the latest version of the Support library,
ActionBar在SettingsActivity中默认不会显示
the action bar doesn't show up by default in the Settings Activity.
最终  要和预想的一样
As a result, it's expected and
使你设备上的程序像这样没有ActionBar
correct that your device looks like this with no action bar.
别担心  在第五课的时候  当我们改变SettingsActivity主题的时候
Don't worry, we'll add the action bar back when we change the theme of
会把ActionBar加回来
the Settings Activity in lesson five.
更多的内容  参考这里的指导信息
For more info, check the instructor notes.